<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://btromm.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://btromm.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2024-05-08T13:47:28+00:00</updated><id>https://btromm.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>Computational neuroscientist interested in using altered states to understand brain dynamics. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">sourdough</title><link href="https://btromm.github.io/blog/2024/sourdough/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="sourdough"/><published>2024-01-08T14:30:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-01-08T14:30:00+00:00</updated><id>https://btromm.github.io/blog/2024/sourdough</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://btromm.github.io/blog/2024/sourdough/"><![CDATA[<p>what is the labor of love, but the foul wind turned palatable?<br/> fermented and bubbly, funky and oozing<br/> the smell of decay becomes umami,<br/> how multi-cultural<br/> it streaks over the surface of cognition,<br/> of waking life</p> <p>what is the labor of love,<br/> but the flow of time turned stagnant<br/> colored red and rosy in the reflection of binoclard being</p> <p>what is the labor of love,<br/> but limbo incarnate?<br/> wherein the preachers and proselytizers beckon and reach out,<br/> declaring judgement day has come<br/> tremoring in fear and righteousness</p> <p>what is the labor of love,<br/> but that present the Bodhisattva philosophizes<br/> that which frees in asymptotic rush<br/> truly, truly it must be</p> <p>truly,<br/> i must think more on the matter<br/> but time, time, time i do not have</p> <p>for labor without love is labor extracted<br/> compacted and distilled,<br/> hollowed metal turned Capital,<br/> its glory filled with heretics<br/> painted targets of sacrifice and encrypted messaging</p> <p>time, time, time to breathe<br/> to bake bread<br/> but slave master calls again<br/> time, time, to paint,<br/> to sing,<br/> to re-enact Eleusinian mysteries<br/> time to make dust the president of the student loans company</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[reflections on labor]]></summary></entry></feed>